// // This page for the questions, answers, options etc;

// let questions = [
//     {
//         numb: 1,
//         question: "What is the real name of Iron Man?",
//         answer: "Tony Stark",
//         options: [
//             "Tony Stark",
//             "Steve Rogers",
//             "Bruce Banner",
//             "Peter Parker"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 2,
//         question: "Who is the king of Wakanda?",
//         answer: "T'Challa",
//         options: [
//             "T'Challa",
//             "M'Baku",
//             "Killmonger",
//             "Shuri"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 3,
//         question: "Which Infinity Stone is in Vision's forehead?",
//         answer: "Mind Stone",
//         options: [
//             "Time Stone",
//             "Mind Stone",
//             "Power Stone",
//             "Reality Stone"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 4,
//         question: "Who is Thor’s adopted brother?",
//         answer: "Loki",
//         options: [
//             "Heimdall",
//             "Loki",
//             "Hela",
//             "Odin"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 5,
//         question: "What is the real name of Black Widow?",
//         answer: "Natasha Romanoff",
//         options: [
//             "Carol Danvers",
//             "Wanda Maximoff",
//             "Natasha Romanoff",
//             "Pepper Potts"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 6,
//         question: "Who was the villain in 'Spider-Man: Homecoming'?",
//         answer: "Vulture",
//         options: [
//             "Green Goblin",
//             "Vulture",
//             "Mysterio",
//             "Doctor Octopus"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 7,
//         question: "What is the name of Peter Quill’s ship?",
//         answer: "Milano",
//         options: [
//             "Starship",
//             "Benatar",
//             "Milano",
//             "Nova"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 8,
//         question: "Which Avenger is a former Russian spy?",
//         answer: "Black Widow",
//         options: [
//             "Black Widow",
//             "Hawkeye",
//             "Scarlet Witch",
//             "Captain Marvel"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 9,
//         question: "Who played the Hulk before Mark Ruffalo?",
//         answer: "Edward Norton",
//         options: [
//             "Edward Norton",
//             "Eric Bana",
//             "David Banner",
//             "Tobey Maguire"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 10,
//         question: "What is Captain America's shield made of?",
//         answer: "Vibranium",
//         options: [
//             "Adamantium",
//             "Vibranium",
//             "Titanium",
//             "Iron"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 11,
//         question: "Who created Ultron?",
//         answer: "Tony Stark",
//         options: [
//             "Bruce Banner",
//             "Steve Rogers",
//             "Tony Stark",
//             "Nick Fury"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 12,
//         question: "What is Doctor Strange’s real name?",
//         answer: "Stephen Strange",
//         options: [
//             "Stephen Strange",
//             "Steven Stark",
//             "Samuel Sterns",
//             "Stephen Lang"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 13,
//         question: "Which Marvel character has a metal arm?",
//         answer: "Winter Soldier",
//         options: [
//             "Falcon",
//             "Winter Soldier",
//             "War Machine",
//             "Hawkeye"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 14,
//         question: "Who is the AI assistant in Iron Man’s suit?",
//         answer: "J.A.R.V.I.S.",
//         options: [
//             "F.R.I.D.A.Y.",
//             "J.A.R.V.I.S.",
//             "K.A.R.E.N.",
//             "A.L.F.R.E.D."
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 15,
//         question: "Which character becomes Star-Lord?",
//         answer: "Peter Quill",
//         options: [
//             "Peter Quill",
//             "Tony Stark",
//             "Stephen Strange",
//             "Bucky Barnes"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 16,
//         question: "Which character is known as the God of Mischief?",
//         answer: "Loki",
//         options: [
//             "Thor",
//             "Loki",
//             "Odin",
//             "Thanos"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 17,
//         question: "Who is the Scarlet Witch?",
//         answer: "Wanda Maximoff",
//         options: [
//             "Wanda Maximoff",
//             "Natasha Romanoff",
//             "Carol Danvers",
//             "Maria Hill"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 18,
//         question: "What is the name of the super soldier serum used on Steve Rogers?",
//         answer: "Super Soldier Serum",
//         options: [
//             "Gamma Radiation",
//             "Extremis",
//             "Super Soldier Serum",
//             "Pym Particles"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 19,
//         question: "Who killed Tony Stark’s parents?",
//         answer: "Winter Soldier",
//         options: [
//             "Loki",
//             "Thanos",
//             "Winter Soldier",
//             "Red Skull"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 20,
//         question: "What is the name of Black Panther’s home?",
//         answer: "Wakanda",
//         options: [
//             "Asgard",
//             "Wakanda",
//             "Xandar",
//             "Sokovia"
//         ]
//     }
// ];


// let questions = [
//     {
//         numb: 1,
//         question: "What is the name of the gang led by Tommy Shelby?",
//         answer: "Peaky Blinders",
//         options: [
//             "Peaky Blinders",
//             "Birmingham Boys",
//             "Sabini Gang",
//             "Black Star"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 2,
//         question: "Which character is a World War I veteran suffering from PTSD?",
//         answer: "Arthur Shelby",
//         options: [
//             "Tommy Shelby",
//             "Arthur Shelby",
//             "John Shelby",
//             "Michael Gray"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 3,
//         question: "What is the name of Tommy Shelby's love interest in Season 1?",
//         answer: "Grace Burgess",
//         options: [
//             "Grace Burgess",
//             "May Carleton",
//             "Lizzie Stark",
//             "Polly Gray"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 4,
//         question: "Who betrays Tommy Shelby in the third season?",
//         answer: "Alfie Solomons",
//         options: [
//             "Alfie Solomons",
//             "Michael Gray",
//             "Billy Kimber",
//             "Luca Changretta"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 5,
//         question: "Who plays the role of Tommy Shelby?",
//         answer: "Cillian Murphy",
//         options: [
//             "Tom Hardy",
//             "Cillian Murphy",
//             "Sam Neill",
//             "Paul Anderson"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 6,
//         question: "In which city is Peaky Blinders primarily set?",
//         answer: "Birmingham",
//         options: [
//             "London",
//             "Liverpool",
//             "Manchester",
//             "Birmingham"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 7,
//         question: "What is the name of the Shelby family matriarch?",
//         answer: "Polly Gray",
//         options: [
//             "Polly Gray",
//             "Ada Shelby",
//             "Lizzie Stark",
//             "Linda Shelby"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 8,
//         question: "Which historical figure does Tommy Shelby meet in Season 2?",
//         answer: "Winston Churchill",
//         options: [
//             "Winston Churchill",
//             "King George",
//             "Benito Mussolini",
//             "Joseph Stalin"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 9,
//         question: "Who is the Italian-American mafia leader in Season 4?",
//         answer: "Luca Changretta",
//         options: [
//             "Al Capone",
//             "Luca Changretta",
//             "Sabini",
//             "Billy Kimber"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 10,
//         question: "What does Tommy Shelby run as a legitimate business front?",
//         answer: "A betting company",
//         options: [
//             "A betting company",
//             "A pub",
//             "A textile mill",
//             "A distillery"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 11,
//         question: "What is Arthur Shelby’s signature weapon?",
//         answer: "Brass knuckles",
//         options: [
//             "A revolver",
//             "A knife",
//             "Brass knuckles",
//             "A baseball bat"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 12,
//         question: "What is the name of Tommy Shelby’s racehorse?",
//         answer: "Grace's Secret",
//         options: [
//             "Grace's Secret",
//             "Dangerous",
//             "May’s Fury",
//             "Shelby’s Pride"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 13,
//         question: "Which political ideology does Tommy Shelby flirt with in later seasons?",
//         answer: "Socialism",
//         options: [
//             "Fascism",
//             "Communism",
//             "Socialism",
//             "Capitalism"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 14,
//         question: "Which of the Shelby brothers dies in Season 4?",
//         answer: "John Shelby",
//         options: [
//             "Tommy Shelby",
//             "Arthur Shelby",
//             "John Shelby",
//             "Finn Shelby"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 15,
//         question: "What year does Peaky Blinders begin in?",
//         answer: "1919",
//         options: [
//             "1914",
//             "1919",
//             "1925",
//             "1930"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 16,
//         question: "Who is the mother of Tommy Shelby’s second child?",
//         answer: "Lizzie Stark",
//         options: [
//             "Grace Burgess",
//             "Lizzie Stark",
//             "Polly Gray",
//             "May Carleton"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 17,
//         question: "What is the nickname of Arthur Shelby’s wife?",
//         answer: "Linda Shelby",
//         options: [
//             "Lizzie",
//             "May",
//             "Grace",
//             "Linda"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 18,
//         question: "Who saves Arthur Shelby from Luca Changretta?",
//         answer: "Tommy Shelby",
//         options: [
//             "Tommy Shelby",
//             "Michael Gray",
//             "Polly Gray",
//             "Alfie Solomons"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 19,
//         question: "Who kills Major Campbell in Season 2?",
//         answer: "Polly Gray",
//         options: [
//             "Tommy Shelby",
//             "Arthur Shelby",
//             "Grace Burgess",
//             "Polly Gray"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 20,
//         question: "What is the main color of the Shelby family’s caps?",
//         answer: "Grey",
//         options: [
//             "Black",
//             "Brown",
//             "Grey",
//             "Blue"
//         ]
//     }
// ];



let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the real name of the Professor?",
        answer: "Sergio Marquina",
        options: [
            "Sergio Marquina",
            "Berlin",
            "Tokyo",
            "Rio"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which city does the heist take place in during the first two parts?",
        answer: "Madrid",
        options: [
            "Barcelona",
            "Madrid",
            "Lisbon",
            "Tokyo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the name of the money that the gang is printing?",
        answer: "Euro",
        options: [
            "Dollar",
            "Euro",
            "Pound",
            "Yen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Who is the character that is known as 'Tokyo'?",
        answer: "Silene Oliveira",
        options: [
            "Tokyo",
            "Lisbon",
            "Nairobi",
            "Helsinki"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the name of the original heist planned by the Professor?",
        answer: "Royal Mint of Spain",
        options: [
            "Bank of Spain",
            "Royal Mint of Spain",
            "Central Bank",
            "Banco de España"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What color are the heist crew's jumpsuits?",
        answer: "Red",
        options: [
            "Black",
            "White",
            "Red",
            "Blue"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which character is the Professor's brother?",
        answer: "Berlin",
        options: [
            "Rio",
            "Berlin",
            "Moscow",
            "Tokyo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the name of the character who is a skilled forger?",
        answer: "Nairobi",
        options: [
            "Nairobi",
            "Denver",
            "Moscow",
            "Helsinki"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which character is known for wearing glasses?",
        answer: "Berlin",
        options: [
            "Moscow",
            "Berlin",
            "Rio",
            "Tokyo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What song does the gang sing during the heist?",
        answer: "Bella Ciao",
        options: [
            "La Cucaracha",
            "Bella Ciao",
            "Auld Lang Syne",
            "Imagine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Who is the head of the hostages during the first heist?",
        answer: "Monica Gaztambide",
        options: [
            "Tokyo",
            "Monica Gaztambide",
            "Raquel Murillo",
            "Nairobi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "What is the main reason behind the heists?",
        answer: "To print money",
        options: [
            "To steal gold",
            "To print money",
            "To fund a revolution",
            "To pay off debts"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "What does 'The Professor' often refer to as his main principle?",
        answer: "Planning",
        options: [
            "Planning",
            "Love",
            "Betrayal",
            "Money"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "What was the name of the character who dies in the second heist?",
        answer: "Nairobi",
        options: [
            "Tokyo",
            "Nairobi",
            "Berlin",
            "Moscow"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Which character is known for their relationship with Tokyo?",
        answer: "Rio",
        options: [
            "Berlin",
            "Helsinki",
            "Rio",
            "Moscow"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "What is the code name for the heist in the Bank of Spain?",
        answer: "The Great Heist",
        options: [
            "The Perfect Heist",
            "The Great Heist",
            "The Royal Heist",
            "The Final Heist"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Who is the police officer that becomes romantically involved with the Professor?",
        answer: "Raquel Murillo",
        options: [
            "Angela",
            "Raquel Murillo",
            "Alicia",
            "Mónica"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "What is the name of the character who is an explosives expert?",
        answer: "Helsinki",
        options: [
            "Berlin",
            "Moscow",
            "Helsinki",
            "Denver"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "What happens to the gold at the end of the series?",
        answer: "They melt it down",
        options: [
            "They hide it",
            "They melt it down",
            "They donate it",
            "They bury it"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "What is the nickname of the police inspector who tries to capture the gang?",
        answer: "The Professor",
        options: [
            "The Colonel",
            "The Professor",
            "The Inspector",
            "The Chief"
        ]
    }
];
